Audrey Beck Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Finance Committee and Fiscal Policy, 1965-1984
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, 1965-1984
    - Finance Committee Records and Notices, 1975-1980 (Box 24:, Folder 893)
    - Finance Committee Statements, 1975-1978 (Box 25:, Folder 894)
    - Finance—Governor's Tax Hearing, 1975 (Box 25:, Folder 895)
    - Finance Public Hearing, 1978 (Box 25:, Folder 896)
    - Finance, Revenue, Bonding Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 897)
    - Finance Surplus, 1977-1978 (Box 25:, Folder 898)
    - Finance Workshop: State tax, 1971-1972 (Box 25:, Folder 899)
    - Fiscal Analysis, Office of, 1975-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 900)
    - Fiscal—Commission on State Tax Revenue, 1982 (Box 25:, Folder 901)
    - Fiscal—Beck, 1974-1976 (Box 25:, Folder 902)
    - Fiscal—Grasso, 1976 (Box 25:, Folder 903)
    - Fiscal notebook, 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 904)
    - Fiscal options, 1981 (Box 25:, Folder 905)
    - Fiscal policy, 1969-1976 (Box 25:, Folder 906)
    - Fiscal policy, 1978-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 907)
    - Fiscal—State Deficits and State Expenditures, 1980-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 908)
    - Gas tax petitions, 1976 (Box 25:, Folder 909)
    - General funds use, 1978-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 910)
    - Income tax, 1981 (Box 25:, Folder 911)
    - Income tax: John Wilson, Goodwin, Sazama, 1969 (Box 25:, Folder 912)
    - Inheritance, Estate, Gift taxes, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 913)
    - Institutional License fees, 1976-1977 (Box 25:, Folder 914)
    - Insurance taxation, 1975-1977 (Box 25:, Folder 915)
    - Leasing property, 1976-1977 (Box 25:, Folder 916)
    - Leasing Sales tax, 1975 (Box 25:, Folder 917)
    - Legislation and budget, 1980-1983 (Box 25:, Folder 918)
    - License Fees, 1976-1977 (Box 25:, Folder 919)
    - Litter tax, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 920)
    - Lotteries, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 921)
    - Monthly estimates, 1978-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 922)
    - Motor Vehicle tax, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 923)
    - Hartford Times: Income tax, 1969 (Box 26:, Folder 924)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1977-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 925)
    - Professional fees, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 926)
    - Projections hearing, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 927)
    - Projections: State fiscal, 1975-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 928)
    - Property tax, 1977-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 929)
    - Property tax, 1979-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 930)
    - Property tax relief study report, 1980-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 931)
    - Public opposition to taxes, 1975-1976 (Box 26:, Folder 932)
    - Railroad tax, 1977-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 933)
    - Reagan Budget, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 934)
    - Reagan Budget and Policy, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 935)
    - Reapportionment, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 936)
    - Revenue alternatives, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 937)
    - Revenue data, 1978-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 938)
    - Revenue Needs Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 939)
    - Sales tax: automobile, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 940)
    - Sales tax: burial equipment, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 941)
    - Sales tax: graphs, 1965-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 942)
    - Sales tax on advertising, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 943)
    - Sales tax on clothing, 1977-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 944)
    - Sales tax on employment services, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 945)
    - Severance tax, 1975-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 946)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, and Marines Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 26:, Folder 947)
    - Special Revenue Commission, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 948)
    - State Bond Commission, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 949)
    - State Bond Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 950-951)
    - State revenue, 1981-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 952)
    - Succession and transfer, 1974-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 953)
    - Surety bonds, 1973-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 954)
    - Surplus (press), 1977-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 955)
    - Tax debate, 1976 (Box 27:, Folder 956)
    - Tax department—Collection data, 1976-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 957)
    - Tax department—Monthly data, 1976-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 958)
    - Tax Increases, 1975 (Box 27:, Folder 959)
    - Tax letters, 1975 (Box 27:, Folder 960)
    - Tax on business services, 1975-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 961)
    - Tax opposition: Manufacturers Association, 1969 (Box 27:, Folder 962)
    - Tax reform, 1969-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 963)
    - Tax reform—Connecticut, 1969-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 964)
    - Tax reform—letters, 1976-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 965)
    - Tax Reform—press, 1969-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 966)
    - Tax symposium, 1975 (Box 27:, Folder 967)
    - Taxation of utilities, 1975-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 968)
    - Taxes OFA information, 1976-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 969)
    - Transport legislation, 1974-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 970)
    - Transportation fees, 1976-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 971)
    - Treasurer, 1979 (Box 27:, Folder 972)
    - Unicorporated business tax, 1981-1982 (Box 27:, Folder 973)
    - Windham Airport Bid, 1977 (Box 27:, Folder 974)
    - Yankee Greyhound Racing and Jai Alai, 1977-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 975)
    - Yedziniak: Income tax on Individuals, Trusts and Estates, undated (Box 27:, Folder 976)
  - Subseries B: School Construction, 1969-1980
    - Auditors, 1975-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 977)
    - Construction, 1969-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 978)
    - Education (Dept. of) circular letters, 1975-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 979)
    - Finance and Education Committee meeting, 1975 (Box 27:, Folder 980)
    - McCoy letter and response, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 981)
    - Numbers—current: School building bonds, 1969-1971 (Box 28:, Folder 982)
    - Paternostro budget, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 983)
    - School construction: bills, 1969-1971 (Box 28:, Folder 984)
    - School construction clippings, 1971-1975 (Box 28:, Folder 985)
    - School construction clippings, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 986)
    - School construction clippings, 1976 (Box 28:, Folder 987-988)
    - School construction clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 989)
    - School construction regulations, 1976 (Box 28:, Folder 990)
    - School grant procedures, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 991)
    - Shedd letters, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 992)
    - State laundries, 1975-1976 (Box 28:, Folder 993)
    - Tepper letter, 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 994)
- Series V: Education, 1951-1983
  - 7712: Retirement, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 995)
  - Accreditation, 1971 (Box 28:, Folder 996)
  - Accredited Private occupational School, 1983 (Box 28:, Folder 997)
  - Adult education, 1966-1970 (Box 28:, Folder 998)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1979-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 999)
  - American Federation of Teachers (AFT) AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 1000)
  - Average Daily Membership (ADM), 1971 (Box 28:, Folder 1001)
  - ASK Project: Area Educational Centers, 1968-1969 (Box 28:, Folder 1002)
  - Bi-lingual Education, 1973 (Box 28:, Folder 1003)
  - Board of Education audit, 1977 (Box 28:, Folder 1004)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1975-1977 (Box 28:, Folder 1005)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 1006-1007)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1980 (Box 28:, Folder 1008-1009)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 1010)
  - Board of Trustees of CT State Colleges, 1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1011)
  - Board of Trustees of Regional Community Colleges, 1979 (Box 29:, Folder 1012)
  - Budget: Education, 1972-1973 (Box 29:, Folder 1013)
  - Budget: Higher Education, 1969 (Box 29:, Folder 1014)
  - Budget: Higher Education, 1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1015)
  - Central Connecticut, 1969-1975 (Box 29:, Folder 1016)
  - Certification of Teachers, 1973 (Box 29:, Folder 1017)
  - Collective bargaining: Public schools, 1970-1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1018)
  - Common, 1973-1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1019)
  - Community College Accreditation, 1972-1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1020)
  - Community Colleges budgets, 1971-1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1021)
  - Community Colleges composition, 1968-1975 (Box 29:, Folder 1022)
  - Connecticut Community Colleges, Congress of, 1982-1983 (Box 29:, Folder 1023)
  - Connecticut Education: Mental Health, 1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1024)
  - Connecticut Education Association (CEA), 1969-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1025)
  - Connecticut Education Association publications, 1963-1970 (Box 29:, Folder 1026)
  - ConnPIRG, 1973 (Box 29:, Folder 1027)
  - Connecticut Law Journal: Horton vs. Meskill, 1976 (Box 29:, Folder 1028)
  - Consumer: Fetterman, 1970-1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1029)
  - Consumer Protection Study: UConn, 1968-1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1030)
  - Day Care: Colleges, 1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1031)
  - Debates: Budget requests, 1978 (Box 29:, Folder 1032)
  - Degree programs, 1969-1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1033)
  - Dissent: Campus, 1969 (Box 29:, Folder 1034)
  - Dissident: Congress, 1969 (Box 29:, Folder 1035)
  - Dissident legislation, 1969-1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1036)
  - Driver training, 1968-1970 (Box 29:, Folder 1037)
  - Drug education, 1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1038)
  - Connecticut, 1973-1975 (Box 29:, Folder 1039)
  - Connecticut State College, 1977-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1040)
  - Education
    - Committee, 1975 (Box 29:, Folder 1041-1043)
    - Committee, 1977 (Box 29:, Folder 1044)
    - Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 29:, Folder 1045)
    - Committee, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 1046)
    - Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1047)
    - Committee: bills raised in Legislature, 1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1048-1049)
    - Committee: UConn problems, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 1050)
  - Education cuts, 1971-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1051)
  - Education—bills and laws, 1973-1981 (Box 30:, Folder 1052)
  - Education—bills and laws, 1979-1980 (Box 30:, Folder 1053)
  - Education, Department of (state), 1973-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1054)
    - Building projects, 1979-1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1055)
  - Education—Newspaper clippings, 1979-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 1056)
  - Education--Statistics, 1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1057)
  - Election laws: Students, 1971 (Box 30:, Folder 1058)
  - Elementary education needs, 1968 (Box 30:, Folder 1059)
  - Enrollment—higher education, 1956-1969 (Box 30:, Folder 1060)
  - Environmental Sciences program, 1968 (Box 30:, Folder 1061)
  - Equalization maps, 1978-1979 (Box 30:, Folder 1062)
  - Faculty—Collective bargaining, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 1063)
  - Faculty correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1064)
  - Fiscal Crisis: New England Higher Education, 1971-1977 (Box 30:, Folder 1065)
  - Food services, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 1066)
  - Food services, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 1067)
  - Greater Hartford Community College, 1972-1977 (Box 30:, Folder 1068)
  - Hartford Seminary, undated (Box 30:, Folder 1069)
  - Hearing, 1977 (Box 30:, Folder 1070)
  - Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 30:, Folder 1071)
  - Higher Education, 1972 (Box 30:, Folder 1072)
  - Higher Education, 1976-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1073)
  - Higher Education, 1979 (Box 30:, Folder 1074)
  - Higher Education, 1979-1980 (Box 30:, Folder 1075)
  - Higher Education, 1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1076)
    - Program Review, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1077)
    - Program Review, 1975-1976 (Box 31:, Folder 1078)
    - Reorganization, 1972-1976 (Box 31:, Folder 1079)
    - Reorganization, 1974-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1080)
    - Reorganization, 1975-1979 (Box 31:, Folder 1081)
    - Reorganization, 1976-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1082)
    - Reorganization, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1083)
    - Structure, 1965-1972 (Box 31:, Folder 1084)
    - Structure, 1971-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1085)
    - Structure, 1975-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1086)
    - Structure, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 1087)
    - Structure, 1976-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1088)
    - Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 31:, Folder 1089)
  - Higher Education, Commission for, 1965-1981 (Box 31:, Folder 1090)
    - Fact Book, 1970 (Box 31:, Folder 1091)
    - Master Plan, 1974-1979 (Box 31:, Folder 1092)
    - Task Force Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1093)
  - Higher Education and the Economy, Governor's Commission on, 1982 (Box 32:, Folder 1094)
  - Home economics, 1975 (Box 32:, Folder 1095)
  - Jencks, C: Co-author Inequality, 1972-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1096)
  - Jobs—Teachers, 1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1097)
  - Joint Teacher Education, 1976 (Box 32:, Folder 1098)
  - Legislation, 1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1099)
  - Legislative Research, Office of, 1981-1982 (Box 32:, Folder 1100)
  - Manchester Community College, 1970-1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1101)
  - Manchester Community College, 1976-1980 (Box 32:, Folder 1102)
  - Manchester Community College: brochures, 1976 (Box 32:, Folder 1103)
  - Master Plan, 1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1104)
  - McCook Hospital, 1972-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1105)
  - Minority Scholarship, 1970-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1106)
  - Mohegan Community College, 1970-1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1107)
  - Mystic Oral School, 1970-1976 (Box 32:, Folder 1108)
  - New England Needs, 1956-1970 (Box 32:, Folder 1109)
  - Northeast Educational Area Resources (NARES), 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 1110)
  - Northeastern Community College, 1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1111)
  - Oceanography, 1972 (Box 32:, Folder 1112)
  - Parking: CT State Employees Association, 1969-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1113)
  - Performance contracting, 1971-1973 (Box 32:, Folder 1114)
  - Personal Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1115)
  - Postsecondary Education California Legislature, Joint Committee on, 1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1116)
  - Private Higher Education, 1969-1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1117)
  - Private school aid, 1969-1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1118)
  - Public college—Fiscal crisis, 1974-1975 (Box 32:, Folder 1119)
  - Quinnipiac, undated (Box 32:, Folder 1120)
  - Quinebaug Valley Community College, 1972-1976 (Box 32:, Folder 1121)
  - Quinebaug Valley Community College, 1977-1981 (Box 32:, Folder 1122)
  - Regional Community College, 1971-1979 (Box 32:, Folder 1123)
  - Regionalization: Elementary and Secondary, 1972 (Box 32:, Folder 1124)
  - Sacred Heart, 1970 (Box 32:, Folder 1125)
  - Salaries: State Technical College, 1968-1975 (Box 32:, Folder 1126)
  - Sazama, Gerald, 1970 (Box 32:, Folder 1127)
  - Scholarships, 1970-1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1128)
  - School bus regulations, 1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1129)
  - School Finance Advisory Panel, 1970-1977 (Box 32:, Folder 1130)
  - School Lunch Program, 1970-1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1131)
  - Segregation, 1969-1971 (Box 32:, Folder 1132)
  - South Central, 1973-1974 (Box 32:, Folder 1133)
  - Special education, 1975-1977 (Box 32:, Folder 1134)
  - Special education: guidelines, 1968-1974 (Box 33:, Folder 1135)
  - State aid to education: Goodwin-Beck, 1963-1981 (Box 33:, Folder 1136)
  - State aid to municipalities, 1980-1981 (Box 33:, Folder 1137)
  - State Board of Education, 1974-1977 (Box 33:, Folder 1138)
  - State Board of Education, 1979-1981 (Box 33:, Folder 1139)
  - State Bond Commission, 1980 (Box 33:, Folder 1140)
  - State Colleges, 1973-1976 (Box 33:, Folder 1141)
  - State Department of Education, 1974-1979 (Box 33:, Folder 1142)
  - Structure of Higher Education, Committee on the, 1976 (Box 33:, Folder 1143)
  - Student Aid Study, 1970-1972 (Box 33:, Folder 1144)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1974-1977 (Box 33:, Folder 1145)
  - Students—Goals and Loans, 1968-1976 (Box 33:, Folder 1146)
  - Summer School Salaries, 1978 (Box 33:, Folder 1147)
  - Superintendents, 1974 (Box 33:, Folder 1148)
  - Teachers, 1977 (Box 33:, Folder 1149)
  - Technical Colleges, 1970-1972 (Box 33:, Folder 1150)
  - Technical Colleges, 1970-1973 (Box 33:, Folder 1151)
  - Technical Colleges: budget, 1975 (Box 33:, Folder 1152)
  - Tenure: Public Schools, 1973 (Box 33:, Folder 1153)
  - Trinity College, undated (Box 33:, Folder 1154)
  - Tunxis Community College, 1967-1976 (Box 33:, Folder 1155)
  - UConn, 1971-1976 (Box 33:, Folder 1156)
  - UConn, 1977-1979 (Box 33:, Folder 1157)
  - UConn, 1980-1981 (Box 33:, Folder 1158)
  - UConn, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 1159)
    - Abortion/Accomplishments, 1968 (Box 33:, Folder 1160)
    - Administration—biographies, 1974 (Box 33:, Folder 1161)
    - Allied Health, 1971-1972 (Box 33:, Folder 1162)
    - Alumni, 1969 (Box 33:, Folder 1163)
    - Anthropology Dept. and Racism, 1974 (Box 33:, Folder 1164)
    - Arjona and UConn pensions, 1967 (Box 33:, Folder 1165)
    - Athletic facilities, 1974-1978 (Box 33:, Folder 1166)
    - Athletics: UConn Club, 1971 (Box 33:, Folder 1167)
    - Bills, 1951-1961 (Box 33:, Folder 1168)
    - Bills, 1969-1972 (Box 33:, Folder 1169)
    - Bills, 1975-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1170)
    - Biobehavioral sciences: UConn, 1970 (Box 34:, Folder 1171)
    - Board of Regents, 1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1172)
    - Bookstore: UConn, 1972-1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1173)
    - Branches: UConn, 1971-1972 (Box 34:, Folder 1174)
    - Branches: UConn letters, 1972 (Box 34:, Folder 1175)
    - Budget: Health Center, 1971 (Box 34:, Folder 1176)
    - Budget: UConn and higher education, 1973-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1177)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1178)
    - Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1179)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1180)
    - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1181)
    - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1182)
    - Budget cuts: Library, 1969 (Box 34:, Folder 1183)
    - Buildings, 1969 (Box 34:, Folder 1184)
    - Campus police, 1969 (Box 34:, Folder 1185)
    - Crime, 1972-1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1186)
    - Dental school, 1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1187)
    - Dining Halls, 1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1188)
    - Dormitory leases, 1969 (Box 34:, Folder 1189)
    - Electric Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1190)
    - Enrollment/Foundation, 1968-1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1191)
    - Ferguson, President, 1973-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1192)
    - Fire Services, 1973-1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1193)
    - Health Center—Farmington, 1968-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1194-1195)
    - Health Center—Private Corporations, 1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1196)
    - Health Center, 1974-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1197)
    - Law School, 1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1198)
    - Law School, 1974-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1199)
    - Legislation, 1973-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1200)
    - Library, 1968-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1201)
    - Library, 1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1202)
    - Liquor permit, 1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1203)
    - Long range planning/Mansfield housing, 1974 (Box 34:, Folder 1204)
    - Management Sciences Laboratory, 1971 (Box 34:, Folder 1205)
    - Marine sciences, 1966-1970 (Box 34:, Folder 1206)
    - Nursing, 1972-1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1207)
    - Parking Fines Dispute, 1969-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1208)
    - Personnel relations, 1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1209)
    - Pollution, 1970 (Box 34:, Folder 1210)
    - Professional Employees, 1972 (Box 34:, Folder 1211)
    - Registration, undated (Box 34:, Folder 1212)
    - Salaries, 1968-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1213)
    - Salaries, 1969-1972 (Box 34:, Folder 1214)
    - Seminary Campus: Law School, 1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1215)
    - Stamford Branch, 1971-1972 (Box 35:, Folder 1216)
    - Summer School, 1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1217)
    - Transfers to UConn, 1971-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1218)
    - Trustees, 1971-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1219)
    - Tuition, 1956-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1220)
    - Tuition, 1974-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1221)
    - Tuition Increases, 1974-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1222)
    - Trustees legislation, 1973-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1223)
    - University Autonomy, 1969 (Box 35:, Folder 1224)
    - University Chronicle, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1225)
    - University Construction Agency, 1969 (Box 35:, Folder 1226)
  - University of Hartford, 1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1227)
  - University of New Haven, 1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1228)
  - Urban Schools, 1968-1969 (Box 35:, Folder 1229)
  - Veterans, 1972-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1230)
  - Veterinary school, 1969-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1231)
  - Vocational education, 1974-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1232)
  - Water Resources Institute, 1971 (Box 35:, Folder 1233)
  - Waterbury Case, 1969 (Box 35:, Folder 1234)
  - Wethersfield School of Law, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1235)
  - Windham Regional Technical Institute, 1972 (Box 35:, Folder 1236)
- Series VI: Women's Issues, 1950-1983
  - Abortion, 1969-1971 (Box 35:, Folder 1237)
  - Abortion, 1972-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1238)
  - Aging—29th, 1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1239)
  - Alert, 1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1240)
  - Alert, 1973-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1241)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1242)
  - AIP-ASPO Women's Rights, 1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1243)
  - ASPO, 1974 (Box 35:, Folder 1244)
  - American Women, Center for, 1973-1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1245)
  - American Women and Politics, Center for, 1972-1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1246)
  - Bandazian, Ann, 1971 (Box 35:, Folder 1247)
  - Beck, Audrey—Speeches, 1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1248)
  - Bicentennial Conference on U.S. Women and Their History, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1249)
  - Business and Professional Women (BPW), 1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1250)
  - Connecticut IWY Conference, 1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1251)
  - Connecticut women in politics, 1971-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1252)
  - Connecticut Women's Congress, 1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1253)
  - Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund (CWEALF), 1972-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1254)
  - Credit Barriers: Women, 1973 (Box 35:, Folder 1255)
  - Daily breakthrough, 1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1256)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1972-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1257)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1978-1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1258)
  - Gratuity Allowance, 1976-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1259)
  - Inequality of sacrifice, 1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1260)
  - International Women's Year, 1975-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1261)
  - International Women's Year (IWY), 1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1262)
  - Labor—women, 1974-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1263)
  - Laurel Girls State, 1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1264)
  - League of Women Voters, 1950-1960s (Box 36:, Folder 1265)
  - League of Women Voters, 1970-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1266)
  - League of Women Voters, 1960-1976 (Box 36:, Folder 1267)
    - Beck Publications, 1960-1976 (Box 36:, Folder 1268)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 36:, Folder 1269)
    - Legislature, 1967-1968 (Box 36:, Folder 1270)
    - Mansfield, 1961-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1271)
    - National Program, 1971-1974 (Box 36:, Folder 1272)
    - State Government, 1962-1974 (Box 36:, Folder 1273)
  - Lectures—Women in Politics, 1973 (Box 36:, Folder 1274)
  - Lectures—Women in Politics, 1972-1973 (Box 36:, Folder 1275)
  - Lectures—Women in Politics, 1972-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1276)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), 1970-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1277)
  - National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 37:, Folder 1278)
  - Newsletter—Democratic Women, 1961-1970 (Box 37:, Folder 1279)
  - Nurse Practice Act, 1974-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1280)
  - OWLS, 1969-1973 (Box 37:, Folder 1281)
  - Pregnancy benefits, 1971-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1282)
  - Rape, 1976-1978 (Box 37:, Folder 1283)
  - Right to life, 1976-1978 (Box 37:, Folder 1284)
  - Service Bureau, 1969-1972 (Box 37:, Folder 1285)
  - Simons, Agnes, 1971-1972 (Box 37:, Folder 1286)
  - Status of Women, Commission on the, 1977-1983 (Box 37:, Folder 1287)
  - Status of Women, Permanent Commission on the (PCSW), 1969-1974 (Box 37:, Folder 1288)
  - Status of Women, Permanent Commission on the (PCSW), 1973-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1289)
  - Status of Women, Permanent Commission on the (PCSW), 1975-1982 (Box 37:, Folder 1290)
  - Weir, Clara, 1978 (Box 37:, Folder 1291)
  - Woodhouse, Chase Going, 1967-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1292)
  - Woman—Leadership Fight, 1971-1972 (Box 37:, Folder 1293)
  - Women, 1955-1972 (Box 37:, Folder 1294)
  - Women, 1971-1980 (Box 37:, Folder 1295)
  - Women, 1972-1974 (Box 37:, Folder 1296)
  - Women, 1974-1976 (Box 37:, Folder 1297)
  - Women, 1974-1978 (Box 37:, Folder 1298)
  - Women, 1976-1977 (Box 37:, Folder 1299)
  - Women, 1976-1978 (Box 38:, Folder 1300)
  - Women, 1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1301)
  - Women, 1979-1980 (Box 38:, Folder 1302)
    - ASPO, 1971-1974 (Box 38:, Folder 1303)
    - Connecticut, 1972-1976 (Box 38:, Folder 1304)
    - Earnings, 1972-1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1305)
    - Planning, 1973 (Box 38:, Folder 1306)